A Guide to the Papers of the Proctor of the University of Virginia, (Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough), 1817-1828
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Deed of land from Daniel A. Piper and Mary A.F. Piper to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, approved by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2069] 1824 April 9, ADS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:352)
- Henry Burkholder to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 April 19, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:353)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1824 April 22, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:354)
- Alex[ander] Garrett to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 April 23, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:355)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2076] 1824 April 27, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:356)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 April 29, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:357)
- F[rancis]; W[alker] Gilmer receipt to Alexander Garrett, approved by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2077] 1824 April 30, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:358)
- John Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 May 3, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:359)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2078] 1824 May 4, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:360)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough with postscript, Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 May 24, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:361)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 May 25, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:362)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 May 28, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:363)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Thomas Jefferson; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2085, item 1 of 2] 1824 June 4, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:364)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Thomas Jefferson [copy of preceding item] [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2085, item 2 of 2] 1824 June 4, AL copy. 3 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:365)
- John H[artwell] Cocke to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 June 5, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:366)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 June 7, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:367)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 June 10, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:368)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 June 14, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:369)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 June 14, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:370)
- D. Hickey to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1824 June 17, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:371)
- Philip. Sturtevant to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1824 June 17, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:372)
- Anthony Bargamin to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 June 21, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:373)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 June 21, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:374)
- N. H. Lewis to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 June 28, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:375)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 July 1, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:376)
- Charles W[illia]m McGuinness to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 July 1, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:377)
- E[dward] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 July 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:378)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 July 6, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:379)
- William T. L. Mason to Ben Austin 1824 July 8, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:380)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Thomas Jefferson; endorsed by T.J. [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2090] 1824 July 14, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:381)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 August 3, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:382)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2092] 1824 August 10, ANS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:383)
- Rob[er]t Johnston & Son to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 August 13, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:384)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough with bill 1824 August 14, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:385)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 August 20, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:386)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 August 24, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:387)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 August 30, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:388)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 September 4, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:389)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 September 16, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:390)
- P. F. B. Constant to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with enclosure of broadside re: Mount Airy College, 1 p 1824 September 20, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:391)
- Agreement between Daniel A. Piper & Mary A.F. Piper and Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough for land purchase 1824 September 22, ADS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:392)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 September 22, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:393)
- Plat of land purchased from Daniel A. and Mary A.F. Piper 1824 September 24, ADS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:394)
- A[ndrew] G. Smith to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 September 27, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:395)
- "Statement on the funds of the University of Virginia and the application of them" 1824 September 30, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:396)
- Balance sheet of the University 1824 September 30, AD, 3 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:397)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 October 4, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:398)
- Agreement for purchase of land - Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough and Daniel A. Piper 1824 October 8, ADS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:399)
- Deed of land purchased by University from Daniel A. Piper and Mary A.F. Piper 1824 October 8, ADS. 4 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:400)
- Geo[rge] W. Spotswood to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 October 10, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:401)
- J[ohn] Gray to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 October 15, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:402)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 October 18, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:403)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to [Thomas Jefferson]; originally enclosed papers re: Board of Visitors meeting; endorsed by T.J. [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2102] 1824 October 28, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:404)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 October 28, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:405)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 November 4, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:406)
- Sam[ue]l C. Faulkner to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 November 5, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:407)
- Robert Johnston & Son to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 November 5, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:408)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 November 8, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:409)
- Andrew Smith to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 November 11, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:410)
- William E. Allen to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1824 November 22, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:411)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Thomas Jefferson re: height of Rotunda dome; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2110] 1824 December 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:412)
- Account of the University with Brockenbrough & Harvie, 1822 December 2-1824 November 6 1824 December 4, AD, 3 p. with dockets (Box-folder 4:413)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 December 4, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:414)
- Thomas Jefferson to A.S.B, with copy of contract between Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough and John Gray, Jr. (sample contract for hotelkeepers), 2 p. [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2113] 1824 December 5, ALS / AD, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:415)
- S. B. Chapman to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 December 19, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:416)
- W[illia]m Bernard to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 December 21, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:417)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1824 December 28, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:418)
- Balance sheet of the University 1824 December 30, AD, 4 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:419)
- Joab Atkinson to John [M.] Perry [1824], ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 4:420)
- Joel Yancey to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] [1824], ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:421)
- Bonds and subscriptions, including bonds of Benjamin Austin, James Dinsmore, Hugh Chisholm, V.W. Southall, and C. Downing and a pledge by Clifton Harris to donate one hundred dollars 1824, ADS. 5 items. (Box-folder 4:422)
- The University of Virginia: Its Origin and Endowment, with inserted invoice for printing signed by Alex[ander] Garrett 1824, Pntd. 4 p. with docket (Box-folder 4:423)
- Workmen's papers - brickmaking, masonry 1824, AD, 3 items. (Box-folder 4:424)
- Miscellaneous accounts 1824, AD, 34 items. (Box-folder 4:425)
- Miscellaneous receipts 1824, ANS. 7 items. (Box-folder 4:426)
- Ja[me]s R. Brooking to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 January 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:427)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with bill 1825 January 8, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:428)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with copy of Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2129] 1824 January 9, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:429)
- W. W. Minor to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 January 10, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:430)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 January 11, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:431)
- B[ernard] Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 January 11, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:432)
- B[ernard] Peyton for W. W. Wilkinson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 January 11, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:433)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 January 19, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:434)
- John Laurance to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 January 19, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:435)
- D[abney] Cosby to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 January 24, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:436)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 January 28, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:437)
- W[illiam] J. Coffee to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 January 31, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:438)
- A[nthony] Bargamin to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 February 4, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 5:439)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 February 8, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:440)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 February 8, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:441)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 February 14, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:442)
- B[ernard] Peyton for W. W. Wilkinson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, and receipt 1825 February 23, signed by W[illia]m Mills 1825 February 16, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:443)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 February 18, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:444)
- S. B. Chapman to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 February 22, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:445)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 February 24, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:446)
- B[ernard] Peyton for W. W. Wilkinson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, and receipt, 1825 March 2, signed by Abraham Danner 1825 February 24, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:447)
- John S. May to James Brockman 1825 February 25, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:448)
- Benj[amin] Collins to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 February 26, ALS, 4 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:449)
- B[ernard] Peyton for W. W. Wilkinson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, and receipt, 1825 March 3, signed by Robert Danner 1825 February 26, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:450)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 February 28, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:451)
- Bernard Peyton to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 March 2, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:452)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough: Statement of the funds of the University as of 1824 December 31; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2155] 1825 March 4, ADS. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:453)
- Ja[me]s Dinsmore and John Neilson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough - cost estimate for furnishing library room 1825 March 5, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:454)
- Thomas Jefferson to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] - draft of newspaper advertisement [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2156] [1825 March 7], AD, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:455)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2158] 1825 March 9, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:456)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with copy of Board of Visitors resolutions [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2159] 1825 March 9, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:457)
- N. & D. Sellers to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 March 9, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:458)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 March 10, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:459)
- John Brockenbrough to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 March 11, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:460)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, 2 copies [original in Jefferson Papers #FC-3055-a] 1825 March 11, Photocopy. 1 p. with address (Box-folder 5:461)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: McAdam road [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2163] 1825 March 16, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:462)
- George Tucker to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 March 18, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:463)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 March 23, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:464)
- Balance sheet of the University 1825 March 31, AD, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:465)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to [Thomas Jefferson], and receipt, 1825 June 17, signed Alex[ander] Garrett. Endorsed by T.J. [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2165] 1825 March 31, ALS, 2:00 PM. (Box-folder 5:466)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2166] 1825 April 2, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:467)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 April 4, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:468)
- W[illiam] Dandridge to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 April 5, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:469)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with statement of account for W. W. Wilkinson 1825 April 5, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:470)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with enclosure from B[rockenbrough] & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 April 15, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:471)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 April 18, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:472)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2173] 1825 April 21, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:473)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with bill 1825 April 25, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:474)
- Robley Dunglison to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 April 28, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:475)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2714] 1825 April 28, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:476)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 May 6, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:477)
- John P. Cobbs to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 May 8, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:478)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with enclosure of handbill draft, AD, 1 p. [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2177] 1825 May 8, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 5:479)
- Deed of land purchased from John M. & Frances T. Perry for University by Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 May 9, ALS, 4 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:480)
- Brockenbrough & Harvie to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 May 13, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:481)
- Bernard Peyton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 May 13, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:482)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with attached receipt, 1825 May 14, signed by John M. Perry, 1 p. with dkt [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2179] 1825 May 14, ADS. 1:00 PM. (Box-folder 5:483)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 May 14, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:484)
- Robley Dunglison to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 May 17, ALS, 1 p. with address (Box-folder 5:485)
- Ja[me]s Byars to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 May 18, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:486)
- John M. Patton to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 May 21, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:487)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2181] 1825 May 22, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:488)
- John B. Richeson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 May 26, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:489)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: McAdam's method of building roads [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2186] 1825 May 31, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:490)
- Circular advertisement, "University of Virginia"; with "cash paid by Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough " for various people 1825 May, Pntd. 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:491)
- John Brockenbrough to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 June 4, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:492)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 June 4, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:493)
- N. Biddle to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with enclosed certification of funds in the Bank of the United States 1825 June 6, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:494)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to [Thomas Jefferson]; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2192] 1825 June 6, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:495)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: Rotunda basement rooms assigned to Dr. Emmet and an oval room to be a museum [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2194] 1825 June 7, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:496)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Thomas Jefferson; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2195] 1825 June 9, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:497)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough; note on verso, [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] to [Thomas Jefferson] [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2196] 1825 June 13, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:498)
- Bern[ar]d Peyton for W. W. Wilkinson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 June 14, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:499)
- Philip. Sturtevant to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 June 18, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:500)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2200] 1825 June 20, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:501)
- John Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 June 27, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:502)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2203] 1825 June 27, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:503)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: stables [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2204] 1825 June 27, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:504)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to [Thomas Jefferson] re: stables; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2205] 1825 June 27, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:505)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2209] 1825 July 2, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:506)
- John B. Richeson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 July 5, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:507)
- W[illiam] Dandridge to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 July 8, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:508)
- John Van Lew & Co. to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with invoice 1825 July 8, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:509)
- Edw[ard] Lowber to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 July 9, ALS, 2 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:510)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 July 9, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:511)
- Ja[me]s Byars to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 July 11, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:512)
- W[illiam] J. Coffee to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough re: cornices 1825 July 12, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:513)
- W[illiam] Dandridge to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 July 14, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:514)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 July 20, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:515)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 July 20, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:516)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2214] 1825 July 23, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:517)
- Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough to Thomas Jefferson re: capitals and cornices; endorsed by Thomas Jefferson [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2215] 1825 July 23, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:518)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2216] 1825 July 24, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:519)
- W[illiam] J. Coffee to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 July 26, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:520)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with receipt, and bill 1825 July 27, ALS, 2 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:521)
- L. A. Pauly to [Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough] 1825 July 30, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:522)
- Th[omas] Boswell to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 August 1, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:523)
- Tho[mas] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, with bills 1825 August 4, ALS, 3 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:524)
- Tho[ma]s May to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 August 4, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:525)
- J[ohn] Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 August 8, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:526)
- John Brockenbrough to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 August 12, ALS, 1 p. with docket (Box-folder 5:527)
- Benj[amin] Blackford to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 August 15, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:528)
- D. W. & C. Warwick to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 August 19, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:529)
- Thomas Jefferson to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough [original in Jefferson Papers #TB-2226] 1825 August 26, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:530)
- Robert Johnson & Son to Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough 1825 August 26, ALS, 1 p. with address, docket (Box-folder 5:531)